planttherapy.com 2017-04-17

# Essential Oils | Plant Therapy: Privacy Policy

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order pages. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, and expiration date) otherwise we cannot process your order. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

We collect personal information not only to fulfill your order, but also to make our services more rewarding for you to use. We usually use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences and improving the customer experience. We may also use your information to contact you for account and promotional purposes.

We do not sell, rent or license any customer personal information.  
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us.

#### Forms That Capture Email Address

By providing this information, you are opting to receive emails from Plant Therapy with news, special offers, promotions and messages tailored to your interests. You may unsubscribe at any time.

#### Questions About Our Privacy Policy

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please [click here](https://www.planttherapy.com/contact-us) to contact us online or see below for our phone number and mailing address:

Plant Therapy Essential Oils  
510 2nd Ave S.  
Twin Falls, ID 83301 US  
Phone: 800-917-6577
